EXPUNSIVE
Kyaa!
So...so goooood...
Ah! Ah! It's nice!
Feels good!
By75
I can't fall over here!
How can this happen?
Don't throw me away!
Now here I am!
I beg you!
I've got nothing to do with it,
I can't take it anymore.
Ah! Ah! Ah!
I'm sleeping! I have a lot of things to do!
The End
When did I get into this room?
Good morning!
Mikuru-chan, good morning.
You're still asleep? It's Onebou-san, right?
Um...
Do you need anything from me?
Mikuru will help you out here from today.
So I'll say hello.
Help?
Yosuke-san!
Hey, Haruka-chan!
Mikuru-chan! You're already sorry for Yosuke-san, aren't you?
Come out quickly!
I'm really sorry.
No, no.
Mikuru-chan is...
Yes?
I feel like I'm getting along well with the old men.
I feel like I'm coming to play with them.
Good morning, Haruka-chan.
Good morning!
Kawahara-kun, good morning.
Huh?
You look pale.
Are you sleepy?
I have something to talk to you about.
Oh, me?
What is it?
I'll be right back.
Then let's go to my room.
Yes.
I'm sorry, Haruka-chan.
I'll be right back.
What's wrong?
Is this room so rare?
Yube is indeed...
in this room.
Mr. Aida's speciality is just the right product.
It's all the same product from the sofa to the carpet.
Well, it's impossible for him to be surprised.
That's not it!
Yube, I saw it!
Are you going to be in this room, Eri-chan?
I knew it.
What you were looking at...
You seem to have a good hobby, too.
That's not it!
What you're doing is...
I'm not making a mistake.
Kiba.
Yes.
E-Eri-chan?
You guys!
Let go of Eri-chan right now!
Stop it, Yosuke-san!
Eri-chan?
That's why I'm telling you that I'm not making a mistake.
I have a debt to pay for Eri's parents.
I'm the one who bought it.
Of course, I'll pay for it myself.
Did you get it?
Don't be stupid!
Let go of Eri-chan!
You still don't get it?
No!
Brother!
That's how it is.
Eri is happy to see you like this in front of you.
You're not a woman like that, Eri.
I don't like it.
Please forgive me.
I...
Eri-chan...
Thanks to Kawahara-kun,
Eri's way of talking is stronger than usual.
Please...
Please forgive me.
This is the main prize for this child.
Now, show it to Kawahara-kun yourself.
I'm so embarrassed.
How long do you want to live?
But...
I feel so good, Yosuke-san.
Can you see me?
Eri's heart is beating so fast.
Look at me, Yosuke-san.
Did you get it all?
Yes, I did.
My heart is beating so fast.
I'm so embarrassed.
No, no, no.
I'm so angry.
You're all...
Kawahara-kun.
Eri is a woman like this,
but in fact, she just lost her virginity.
That person is...
What did she want to say?
Yosuke-san.
No, what's wrong?
Um, did you see Natsuki-san?
Natsuki-san?
Yes, I can't see her from the morning.
Natsuki-san...
I haven't seen her today either.
Is that so?
What's wrong?
No, nothing.
Let's ask the director.
I have some business to do.
Please.
Damn, I can't help it.
Yosuke-san?
Then, see you later.
Yosuke-san...
He's staring at me all the time.
Mikuru-chan!
Haruka-chan, I like you.
W-What are you talking about?
You don't have to hide it.
You seem to be kind to me.
Mikuru likes you too.
It's okay.
I won't take Mikuru.
No one said that.
Natsuki-san?
I came to take a break because I have something to do.
Something to do? What is it?
Well, I didn't ask you in detail.
More importantly, I came to see you.
What do you think?
Give it to me.
You're strong.
You know Saeko-san, don't you?
Aida-san.
Aida-san?
Don't run away from me.
I'm going to call her Eri from the facility Helper.
You want me to be a toy?
Why are you leaving after knowing?
What do you want to do?
What?
Aida-san and her are all related, aren't they?
That's strange.
You...
I just want to say that I'm crazy.
What?
I want to play with my body.
That's from you?
If you're going to lie down, you'll always lie down, right?
You're the same.
In the bottom of your heart,
the body of a woman is the only thing you want.
Excuse me.
That's right. You're the only thing you want.
That's why you came here.
Yes.
I think you did a good job.
It's a matter of time before you can leave.
You couldn't even see the reaction of the Kami village during the summer.
No, it's just that I'm a little tired from the cruel work.
I'm not as busy as I used to be.
See you later.
How long have you been like this?
You're late.
It's strange that I came here.
Here?
What is it?
You're doing it.
For me?
I'm doing it.
Onii-chan!
Thank you for your hard work.
No, thank you.
Tomi-san!
Oh, no.
Haruka-chan, it's about Natsuki-san.
Is that so?
If that's the case, can you say something to me?
I think it was a request.
Natsuki-onee-chan said she was looking forward to working with Mikuru.
She'll come back tomorrow.
By the way, is Mikuru-chan staying?
Onii-chan and I stayed in the room together.
Mikuru-chan!
I'm sorry.
I decided to stay in my room.
Were you disappointed?
Well...
Natsuki-san?
Wait a minute!
Where?
Mikuru-chan, isn't it narrow?
I can sleep on the floor.
No, Haruka-onee-chan and I are in the same room.
It's too much.
Hey! What are you doing?
I thought you were big.
Don't make fun of me.
Okay.
Video tape?
That person is...
It hurts!
That voice!
Natsuki-san?
Natsuki-san!
Hey, Onee-chan.
Have you ever had sex?
What are you saying all of a sudden?
I've never had sex, but I wonder if it feels good.
I don't know about that.
Don't say that. Go to sleep.
Mikuru-chan?
I feel dizzy.
What's wrong with me again?
Mikuru-chan, I'm kidding!
Onee-chan...
Actually, I just lost my husband.
The other guy...
It's a dream.
It wasn't a dream, was it?
Oh, he was talking about me.
Eri-chan.
It's a dream!
Onee-chan, you're so cute.
Tell me how you feel.
Why do I feel dizzy?
Onee-chan, you're the same as Mikuru-chan.
I'm sorry.
But don't do this!
Aida, I'm talking to you!
Wh-Who are you?
Natsuki-san?
I've been waiting for you.
Look, Natsuki-san.
It's you, Yosuke-san.
Eri-chan, what are you doing?
Natsuki-san, you don't have to touch me.
You're already overflowing.
It's only been a day since you were taken away by Yosuke-san.
Why did Eri-chan order you to do this?
Why did she order you to do this?
Natsuki-san, you're the same as me.
You're the same as me.
Yosuke-san, it's not good to mess with yourself.
You're always overflowing.
You're so cute.
Natsuki-san, you open and close embarrassing things.
It's like you're having a snack.
Don't you think Natsuki-san is cute?
You think so, don't you, Yosuke-san?
I'm telling the truth.
That's right. I am.
You don't want to be in this, do you?
Please, I can't stand it anymore.
Please, please.
I want to get into that.
I'm not going to get lost.
Look, this person.
What are you trying to hide?
I'm not like that.
Natsuki-san, you're so cute.
You're so cute.
Please, I can't stand it anymore.
I'm not going to get lost.
You're the same as me.
I'm scared!
I'm just kidding.
I'll stab my finger several times from the beginning.
No!
If it's this wet, I don't need lotion.
It's not that fast!
Aina, I'm sure of it.
It's not over yet.
Aina!
Wow!
I can't believe I'm in my stomach!
Why?
I'm full!
Yosuke!
I'm going too!
I'm going to seduce a woman!
Wow!
Mikuru, don't be like that!
It's too hot for me to breathe.
It feels good.
Mikuru, are you sulking?
Why?
Stop it already!
You're sulking too, Aina.
That's not right!
What?
Aina, are you feeling good?
I'm just kidding.
It's too hot for me to breathe.
I'm going to seduce a woman!
Mikuru, don't be like that!
It feels so good!
I'm going to seduce a woman!
Mikuru, don't be like that!
Hehehehe...
Well, you still don't have enough blood?
Yeah...
You're the reason you were so tired.
And you haven't had enough bile for a while, after all?
Not enough?
That's right.
I wouldn't keep doing what I really want to do.
Yosuke would really want to send Haruka away, wouldn't he?
I'm sure you want to do it with your spirit, don't you?
Haruka... Haruka...
I'm sure he's waiting for you, Yosuke.
He's waiting for me?
Yes, he's waiting for me.
I'm going to make him wet because he's bored.
I want you to make him feel alive.
Haruka...
Why did Mikuru...
do this to me?
Haruka...
Yosuke?
W-What's going on at this hour?
No, don't come in!
You've been waiting for me, Haruka.
No, Yosuke!
Y-You're kidding, aren't you, Yosuke?
No!
What's wrong, Yosuke?
Please, stop it!
You want me to do this to you, don't you?
I'm sure you want me to do this to you, don't you?
No!
I-I don't want you to do this to me!
Please, stop it!
It hurts!
Don't move!
It breaks!
Please, stop it!
It hurts!
If you do this to me...
Why?
It hurts!
I'm the one who did this.
I've been lying to you.
Mikuru...
Please, don't hurt me.
It hurts!
No!
I'm going to be weird!
What should I do?
No!
I'm so embarrassed!
Yosuke...
It hurts!
Yosuke!
It hurts so much!
I can't stand it!
It hurts!
Please, stop it!
Yosuke!
It hurts!
It hurts so much!
It hurts.
It hurts!
Why is it like this again?
Did you understand it?
It's all my fault.
Everything is in order.
That's right.
But this time, as planned...
The tiger has escaped.
It was faster than I thought.
Yes!
The tiger's tail was...
It was fun.
Please forgive me for this.
No.
It's still too early.
Please forgive me.
I can't take it anymore.
I don't want to see you again.
Please.
Let's go.
Please forgive me.